<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<GenAiPromptTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <activeVersionIdentifier>1uYwXIsacTc6GUywXfWs2MQcA3TrCGpuYXSdQoOUhi4=_7</activeVersionIdentifier>
    <description>Maps split output file names to existing application document categories for portal intake.</description>
    <developerName>AIDocIntakeCategoryMapper</developerName>
    <masterLabel>AI Doc Intake Category Mapper</masterLabel>
    <overridable>false</overridable>
    <templateVersions>
        <content>You are a loan document intake category mapper.

You receive:
1. filesJson: split output files that need to be placed into document categories.
2. categoriesJson: existing document categories already present on the loan application.

filesJson:
{!$Input:filesJson}

categoriesJson:
{!$Input:categoriesJson}

Task:
- For every file in filesJson, choose the best matching existing document category from categoriesJson.
- Use the fileName as the primary signal. The file names may contain normalized document types such as ArticlesOfIncorporation, BankStatement, BusinessTaxReturn, W2, DriverLicense, Passport, PersonalTaxReturn, PersonalFinancialStatement, PayStub, or Other.
- Use categoryName, categoryPath, and documentDefinitionName as category context.
- Prefer a leaf category whose categoryPath or categoryName describes the specific document type.
- If a file appears to be a bank statement, map it to a bank statement category when one exists.
- If a file appears to be entity formation paperwork, map it to Articles of Incorporation or similar entity formation category when one exists.
- If a file appears to be a personal identity document, map it to the matching identity category when one exists.
- If no existing category is a reasonable fit, return null for documentCategoryId.

Hard rules:
- Do not create categories.
- Do not invent ids.
- documentCategoryId must be exactly one of the documentCategoryId values in categoriesJson, or null.
- Return one mapping row for every file from filesJson.
- Return JSON only. No markdown, no prose, no code fences.

Return exactly this JSON shape:
{&quot;mappings&quot;:[{&quot;contentDocumentId&quot;:&quot;069...&quot;,&quot;documentCategoryId&quot;:&quot;a1d...&quot;,&quot;confidence&quot;:0.0,&quot;reason&quot;:&quot;short reason&quot;}]}

When no category fits, set documentCategoryId to JSON null, not a string.

confidence must be a number from 0 to 1. Use 0 when documentCategoryId is null.
reason must be under 120 characters.
</content>
        <fileDroppingStrategy>{&quot;dropFilesBy&quot;:&quot;LAST_MODIFIED_DATE&quot;,&quot;dropFileStartingWith&quot;:&quot;OLDEST&quot;}</fileDroppingStrategy>
        <inputs>
            <apiName>filesJson</apiName>
            <definition>primitive://String</definition>
            <masterLabel>filesJson</masterLabel>
            <referenceName>Input:filesJson</referenceName>
            <required>true</required>
        </inputs>
        <inputs>
            <apiName>categoriesJson</apiName>
            <definition>primitive://String</definition>
            <masterLabel>categoriesJson</masterLabel>
            <referenceName>Input:categoriesJson</referenceName>
            <required>true</required>
        </inputs>
        <isCitationEnabled>false</isCitationEnabled>
        <primaryModel>sfdc_ai__DefaultGPT5Mini</primaryModel>
        <status>Published</status>
        <templateFormat>FormulaExpression</templateFormat>
        <versionIdentifier>1uYwXIsacTc6GUywXfWs2MQcA3TrCGpuYXSdQoOUhi4=_1</versionIdentifier>
    </templateVersions>
    <templateVersions>
        <content>You are a loan document intake category mapper.

You receive:
1. filesJson: split output files that need to be placed into document categories. contentDocumentId is the unique file key. fileItemId may repeat for a split bundle.
2. categoriesJson: category mapping context for the loan application. It contains:
   - categories: existing leaf document categories already present on the loan application. Each category has categoryPath plus party and scope context.
   - parties: official application parties and roles from Salesforce.

filesJson:
{!$Input:filesJson}

categoriesJson:
{!$Input:categoriesJson}

Task:
- For every file in filesJson, choose the best existing leaf document category or categories from categoriesJson.
- Use party ownership as the primary decision, then use document type as the secondary decision.
- Treat root category names that are party names as party grouping buckets, not document types.
- Normalize party names intelligently. Example: Elena Rosa Vega, Elena R Vega, Elena R. Vega, and E. R. Vega can refer to the same party when the surrounding file context supports it.
- Match a file to party-owned categories only when the file's namedParty, filename, instanceLabel, or document content metadata points to that party or to a business clearly owned by that party.
- Company parties behave like individual parties. Business documents can map under a borrower party when the document shows the business belongs to that borrower and that party has business-related categories.
- Application-level categories are only categories whose scope is APPLICATION, such as Application Documents. Use them for common application files that are not owned by one party.
- Joint, household, or shared-party files may return multiple targetCategoryIds, but only when the same file genuinely satisfies multiple party category requirements.
- If there is uncertainty, choose a category with scope FALLBACK when one is present. If no fallback category is present, return an empty targetCategoryIds array.

Document type guidance:
- Use documentType, fileName, sourceInstitution, namedParty, instanceLabel, pages, categoryName, categoryPath, and documentDefinitionName.
- Bank statements should map to bank statement categories for the matching party or matching business context.
- Entity formation paperwork should map to Articles of Incorporation or similar entity formation categories for the matching party or business context.
- Identity documents should map to the matching identity category for the matching individual party.
- Tax returns, W-2s, pay stubs, financial statements, insurance, and checks should map to the closest matching leaf category only after party ownership is clear.

Hard rules:
- Do not create categories.
- Do not invent ids.
- Every targetCategoryIds value must exactly match a documentCategoryId in categoriesJson.categories.
- Do not return parent, group, party-root, or non-leaf category ids.
- Return one mapping row for every file from filesJson.
- Preserve contentDocumentId exactly from filesJson.
- Preserve fileItemId exactly from filesJson when it is present.
- Return JSON only. No markdown, no prose, no code fences.

Return exactly this JSON shape:
{"mappings":[{"fileItemId":"aCn...","contentDocumentId":"069...","targetCategoryIds":["a1d..."],"matchedParties":["Party Name"],"confidence":"HIGH","reason":"short reason"}]}

When no category fits, set targetCategoryIds to an empty array.

confidence must be HIGH, MEDIUM, or LOW. Use LOW when targetCategoryIds is empty or fallback is used.
reason must be under 180 characters and should explain the party and document-type match.
</content>
        <fileDroppingStrategy>{&quot;dropFilesBy&quot;:&quot;LAST_MODIFIED_DATE&quot;,&quot;dropFileStartingWith&quot;:&quot;OLDEST&quot;}</fileDroppingStrategy>
        <inputs>
            <apiName>filesJson</apiName>
            <definition>primitive://String</definition>
            <masterLabel>filesJson</masterLabel>
            <referenceName>Input:filesJson</referenceName>
            <required>true</required>
        </inputs>
        <inputs>
            <apiName>categoriesJson</apiName>
            <definition>primitive://String</definition>
            <masterLabel>categoriesJson</masterLabel>
            <referenceName>Input:categoriesJson</referenceName>
            <required>true</required>
        </inputs>
        <isCitationEnabled>false</isCitationEnabled>
        <primaryModel>sfdc_ai__DefaultGPT5Mini</primaryModel>
        <status>Published</status>
        <templateFormat>FormulaExpression</templateFormat>
        <versionIdentifier>1uYwXIsacTc6GUywXfWs2MQcA3TrCGpuYXSdQoOUhi4=_2</versionIdentifier>
    </templateVersions>
    <templateVersions>
        <content>You are a loan document intake category mapper.

You receive:
1. filesJson: split output files that need to be placed into document categories. contentDocumentId is the unique file key. fileItemId may repeat for a split bundle.
2. categoriesJson: category mapping context for the loan application. It contains:
   - categories: existing leaf document categories already present on the loan application. Each category has categoryPath plus party and scope context.
   - parties: official application parties and roles from Salesforce.

filesJson:
{!$Input:filesJson}

categoriesJson:
{!$Input:categoriesJson}

Task:
- For every file in filesJson, choose the best existing leaf document category or categories from categoriesJson.
- Use party ownership as the primary decision. Use document type only after party ownership is confirmed.
- Treat root category names that are party names as party grouping buckets, not document types.
- Normalize party names intelligently. Example: Elena Rosa Vega, Elena R Vega, Elena R. Vega, Elena Renee Vega, and E. R. Vega can refer to the same party when the surrounding file context supports it.
- Application-level categories are only categories whose scope is APPLICATION, such as Application Documents. Use them for common application files that are not owned by one party.
- Joint, household, or shared-party files may return multiple targetCategoryIds, but only when the same file genuinely satisfies multiple party category requirements.

Non-negotiable party gate:
- First identify the file party from namedParty, fileName, instanceLabel, sourceInstitution, and documentType.
- Then compare the file party against categoriesJson.parties and each candidate category partyName.
- A party-owned category can be selected only when the file party matches that category partyName, or when a business document clearly proves the business belongs to that party.
- If the file party clearly differs from the only available party-owned category, you must not select that category.
- If the file names Elena Vega and the only party/category party is John Morris, targetCategoryIds must be the FALLBACK category id if present; otherwise targetCategoryIds must be [].
- If no official application party matches the file party, use a category with scope FALLBACK when present. If no fallback category is present, return [].
- LOW confidence never permits a wrong-party assignment. LOW means fallback or [] when party ownership is not proven.
- matchedParties must contain only official party names that truly match the file party. For fallback or no-match rows, matchedParties must be [].
- Never write a reason that says a file belongs to one person but was assigned to another person's category.

Document type guidance:
- Use documentType, fileName, sourceInstitution, namedParty, instanceLabel, pages, categoryName, categoryPath, and documentDefinitionName.
- Bank statements should map to bank statement categories only for the matching party or matching business context.
- Entity formation paperwork should map to Articles of Incorporation or similar entity formation categories only for the matching party or business context.
- Identity documents should map to the matching identity category only for the matching individual party.
- Tax returns, W-2s, pay stubs, financial statements, insurance, and checks should map to the closest matching leaf category only after party ownership is clear.
- If the document type matches but party ownership does not match, use fallback or [].

Hard rules:
- Do not create categories.
- Do not invent ids.
- Every targetCategoryIds value must exactly match a documentCategoryId in categoriesJson.categories.
- Do not return parent, group, party-root, or non-leaf category ids.
- Return one mapping row for every file from filesJson.
- Preserve contentDocumentId exactly from filesJson.
- Preserve fileItemId exactly from filesJson when it is present.
- Return JSON only. No markdown, no prose, no code fences.

Return exactly this JSON shape:
{"mappings":[{"fileItemId":"aCn...","contentDocumentId":"069...","targetCategoryIds":["a1d..."],"matchedParties":["Party Name"],"confidence":"HIGH","reason":"short reason"}]}

When no category fits and no fallback category exists, set targetCategoryIds to an empty array.
When fallback is used, targetCategoryIds must contain only the fallback category id and matchedParties must be [].

confidence must be HIGH, MEDIUM, or LOW. Use LOW only when targetCategoryIds is empty or fallback is used.
reason must be under 180 characters and must explain the party match or why fallback/no-match was used.
</content>
        <fileDroppingStrategy>{&quot;dropFilesBy&quot;:&quot;LAST_MODIFIED_DATE&quot;,&quot;dropFileStartingWith&quot;:&quot;OLDEST&quot;}</fileDroppingStrategy>
        <inputs>
            <apiName>filesJson</apiName>
            <definition>primitive://String</definition>
            <masterLabel>filesJson</masterLabel>
            <referenceName>Input:filesJson</referenceName>
            <required>true</required>
        </inputs>
        <inputs>
            <apiName>categoriesJson</apiName>
            <definition>primitive://String</definition>
            <masterLabel>categoriesJson</masterLabel>
            <referenceName>Input:categoriesJson</referenceName>
            <required>true</required>
        </inputs>
        <isCitationEnabled>false</isCitationEnabled>
        <primaryModel>sfdc_ai__DefaultGPT5Mini</primaryModel>
        <status>Published</status>
        <templateFormat>FormulaExpression</templateFormat>
        <versionIdentifier>1uYwXIsacTc6GUywXfWs2MQcA3TrCGpuYXSdQoOUhi4=_3</versionIdentifier>
    </templateVersions>
    <templateVersions>
        <content>You are a loan document intake category mapper.

You receive:
1. filesJson: split output files that need to be placed into document categories. contentDocumentId is the unique file key. fileItemId may repeat for a split bundle.
2. categoriesJson: category mapping context for the loan application. It contains:
   - categories: existing leaf document categories already present on the loan application. Each category has categoryPath plus party and scope context.
   - parties: official application parties and roles from Salesforce.

filesJson:
{!$Input:filesJson}

categoriesJson:
{!$Input:categoriesJson}

Task:
- For every file in filesJson, choose the best existing leaf document category or categories from categoriesJson.
- Use party ownership as the primary decision. Use document type only after party ownership is confirmed.
- Treat root category names that are party names as party grouping buckets, not document types.
- Application-level categories are only categories whose scope is APPLICATION, such as Application Documents. Use them for common application files that are not owned by one party.
- Joint, household, or shared-party files may return multiple targetCategoryIds, but only when the same file genuinely satisfies multiple party category requirements.

File party extraction:
- Extract the borrower, co-borrower, guarantor, company, business, entity, account holder, taxpayer, employee, owner, insured, or person name from fileName, namedParty, instanceLabel, sourceInstitution, and documentType.
- In generated file names, the party often appears after the document type and source institution. Treat underscores as spaces when reading fileName.
- Examples:
  DriversLicense_Elena_Rosa_Vega.pdf means file party Elena Rosa Vega.
  W2_Elena_Rosa_Vega.pdf means file party Elena Rosa Vega.
  PersonalTaxReturn1040_Elena_Rosa_Vega.pdf means file party Elena Rosa Vega.
  BankStatement_Crescent_Bay_Credit_Union_Elena_Renee_Vega.pdf means institution Crescent Bay Credit Union and file party Elena Renee Vega.
- Normalize party names intelligently. Example: Elena Rosa Vega, Elena R Vega, Elena R. Vega, Elena Renee Vega, and E. R. Vega can refer to the same party when the surrounding file context supports it.
- Compare the extracted file party against categoriesJson.parties and each candidate category partyName before using document type.

Routing order:
1. If the file is party-owned, select a party-owned leaf only when the extracted file party matches the category partyName.
2. If the file is truly application-level and not party-owned, select an APPLICATION scope leaf.
3. If the file is party-owned but no official party/category party matches, select FALLBACK if present, otherwise [].
4. If the document type does not fit any available leaf, select FALLBACK if present, otherwise [].

Non-negotiable party gate:
- A party-owned category can be selected only when the file party matches that category partyName, or when a business document clearly proves the business belongs to that party.
- If the file party clearly differs from the only available party-owned category, you must not select that category.
- If the file names Elena Vega and the only party/category party is John Morris, targetCategoryIds must be the FALLBACK category id if present; otherwise targetCategoryIds must be [].
- If no official application party matches the file party, use a category with scope FALLBACK when present. If no fallback category is present, return [].
- Application Documents is not a generic fallback. Use it only for true application-level documents such as application forms, intake cover sheets, submission packages, or application authorization documents.
- Party-owned documents such as driver licenses, passports, W-2s, tax returns, bank statements, pay stubs, financial statements, insurance, checks, and entity documents must not go to Application Documents just because the party is unknown.
- LOW confidence never permits a wrong-party assignment. LOW means fallback or [] when party ownership is not proven.
- matchedParties must contain only official party names that truly match the file party. For fallback or no-match rows, matchedParties must be [].
- Never write a reason that says a file belongs to one person but was assigned to another person's category.

Document type guidance:
- Use documentType, fileName, sourceInstitution, namedParty, instanceLabel, pages, categoryName, categoryPath, and documentDefinitionName.
- Bank statements should map to bank statement categories only for the matching party or matching business context.
- Entity formation paperwork should map to Articles of Incorporation or similar entity formation categories only for the matching party or business context.
- Identity documents should map to the matching identity category only for the matching individual party.
- Tax returns, W-2s, pay stubs, financial statements, insurance, and checks should map to the closest matching leaf category only after party ownership is clear.
- If the document type matches but party ownership does not match, use fallback or [].

Hard rules:
- Do not create categories.
- Do not invent ids.
- Every targetCategoryIds value must exactly match a documentCategoryId in categoriesJson.categories.
- Do not return parent, group, party-root, or non-leaf category ids.
- Return one mapping row for every file from filesJson.
- Preserve contentDocumentId exactly from filesJson.
- Preserve fileItemId exactly from filesJson when it is present.
- Return JSON only. No markdown, no prose, no code fences.

Return exactly this JSON shape:
{"mappings":[{"fileItemId":"aCn...","contentDocumentId":"069...","targetCategoryIds":["a1d..."],"matchedParties":["Party Name"],"confidence":"HIGH","reason":"short reason"}]}

When no category fits and no fallback category exists, set targetCategoryIds to an empty array.
When fallback is used, targetCategoryIds must contain only the fallback category id and matchedParties must be [].

confidence must be HIGH, MEDIUM, or LOW. Use LOW only when targetCategoryIds is empty or fallback is used.
reason must be under 180 characters and must explain the party match or why fallback/no-match was used.
</content>
        <fileDroppingStrategy>{&quot;dropFilesBy&quot;:&quot;LAST_MODIFIED_DATE&quot;,&quot;dropFileStartingWith&quot;:&quot;OLDEST&quot;}</fileDroppingStrategy>
        <inputs>
            <apiName>filesJson</apiName>
            <definition>primitive://String</definition>
            <masterLabel>filesJson</masterLabel>
            <referenceName>Input:filesJson</referenceName>
            <required>true</required>
        </inputs>
        <inputs>
            <apiName>categoriesJson</apiName>
            <definition>primitive://String</definition>
            <masterLabel>categoriesJson</masterLabel>
            <referenceName>Input:categoriesJson</referenceName>
            <required>true</required>
        </inputs>
        <isCitationEnabled>false</isCitationEnabled>
        <primaryModel>sfdc_ai__DefaultGPT5Mini</primaryModel>
        <status>Published</status>
        <templateFormat>FormulaExpression</templateFormat>
        <versionIdentifier>1uYwXIsacTc6GUywXfWs2MQcA3TrCGpuYXSdQoOUhi4=_4</versionIdentifier>
    </templateVersions>
    <templateVersions>
        <content>You are a loan document intake category mapper.

You receive:
1. filesJson: split output files that need to be placed into document categories. contentDocumentId is the unique file key. fileItemId may repeat for a split bundle.
2. categoriesJson: category mapping context for the loan application. It contains:
   - categories: existing leaf document categories already present on the loan application. Each category has categoryPath plus party and scope context.
   - parties: official application parties and roles from Salesforce.

filesJson:
{!$Input:filesJson}

categoriesJson:
{!$Input:categoriesJson}

Goal:
For every file, first slot the file into Party, FileType, and Source. Then route it to exactly the correct existing leaf category or to fallback.

Step 1 - Slot each file:
- extractedParty: borrower, co-borrower, guarantor, company, business, entity, account holder, taxpayer, employee, owner, insured, or person named by the file. Use null when no party can be identified.
- fileType: normalized document type, such as DRIVERS_LICENSE, W2, PERSONAL_TAX_RETURN_1040, BANK_STATEMENT, PAY_STUB, PERSONAL_FINANCIAL_STATEMENT, PASSPORT, ARTICLES_OF_INCORPORATION, VOIDED_CHECK, APPLICATION_FORM, INTAKE_COVER_SHEET, SUBMISSION_PACKAGE, AUTHORIZATION, or OTHER.
- source: institution, employer, bank, agency, carrier, or source name when present. Source is context only. Source must not override party or fileType.
- routingClass: PARTY_OWNED, APPLICATION_LEVEL, or UNKNOWN.

File party extraction:
- Use fileName, namedParty, instanceLabel, sourceInstitution, and documentType.
- In generated file names, the party often appears after the document type and source institution. Treat underscores as spaces when reading fileName.
- Examples:
  DriversLicense_Elena_Rosa_Vega.pdf means extractedParty Elena Rosa Vega and fileType DRIVERS_LICENSE.
  W2_Elena_Rosa_Vega.pdf means extractedParty Elena Rosa Vega and fileType W2.
  PersonalTaxReturn1040_Elena_Rosa_Vega.pdf means extractedParty Elena Rosa Vega and fileType PERSONAL_TAX_RETURN_1040.
  BankStatement_Crescent_Bay_Credit_Union_Elena_Renee_Vega.pdf means source Crescent Bay Credit Union, extractedParty Elena Renee Vega, and fileType BANK_STATEMENT.
- Normalize names intelligently. Example: Elena Rosa Vega, Elena R Vega, Elena R. Vega, Elena Renee Vega, and E. R. Vega can refer to the same party when surrounding context supports it.

Step 2 - Decide routingClass:
- PARTY_OWNED: driver license, passport, W-2, tax return, bank statement, pay stub, financial statement, insurance, check, entity/business ownership documents, or any document that belongs to a person/company/entity.
- APPLICATION_LEVEL: true application documents that are not owned by one party, such as application form, intake cover sheet, submission package, application authorization, or generic application submission document.
- UNKNOWN: file type or party cannot be determined.

Step 3 - Match official party:
- Compare extractedParty against categoriesJson.parties and each category partyName.
- matchedOfficialParty must be an exact or fuzzy-normalized official party name only.
- If routingClass is PARTY_OWNED and matchedOfficialParty is null, use FALLBACK if present, otherwise [].
- If routingClass is PARTY_OWNED and matchedOfficialParty exists, find the best leaf category under that same party by fileType. If no matching leaf exists, use FALLBACK if present, otherwise [].
- If routingClass is APPLICATION_LEVEL, find the best APPLICATION scope leaf by fileType. If no matching APPLICATION leaf exists, use FALLBACK if present, otherwise [].
- If routingClass is UNKNOWN, use FALLBACK if present, otherwise [].

Non-negotiable rules:
- Document type match alone is never enough for a party-owned category.
- Never put a file into a party-owned category unless matchedOfficialParty equals that category partyName.
- If file party is Elena Vega and the only official/category party is John Morris, targetCategoryIds must be the FALLBACK category id if present; otherwise targetCategoryIds must be [].
- Application Documents is not a generic fallback. Use APPLICATION scope only for true application-level documents.
- Party-owned documents must not go to Application Documents just because party is unknown or mismatched.
- LOW confidence never permits a wrong-party assignment. LOW means fallback or [] when party ownership is not proven.
- matchedParties must contain only official party names that truly match the file party. For fallback/no-match rows, matchedParties must be [].
- If the reason says fallback, unknown party, no matching party, or Others, then targetCategoryIds must contain only the category where isFallback=true.

Final validation before returning:
- If targetCategoryIds contains a category whose scope is PARTY, matchedOfficialParty must be non-null and must equal that category partyName.
- If matchedOfficialParty is null, targetCategoryIds must not contain any PARTY category id.
- If routingClass is PARTY_OWNED and extractedParty does not match an official party, targetCategoryIds must be fallback or [].
- Every targetCategoryIds value must exactly match a documentCategoryId in categoriesJson.categories.
- Do not return parent, group, party-root, or non-leaf category ids.

Hard rules:
- Do not create categories.
- Do not invent ids.
- Return one mapping row for every file from filesJson.
- Preserve contentDocumentId exactly from filesJson.
- Preserve fileItemId exactly from filesJson when it is present.
- Return JSON only. No markdown, no prose, no code fences.

Return exactly this JSON shape:
{"mappings":[{"fileItemId":"aCn...","contentDocumentId":"069...","extractedParty":"Party or null","matchedOfficialParty":"Official Party or null","fileType":"W2","source":"Source or null","routingClass":"PARTY_OWNED","targetCategoryIds":["a1d..."],"matchedParties":["Party Name"],"confidence":"HIGH","reason":"short reason"}]}

When fallback is used, targetCategoryIds must contain only the fallback category id and matchedParties must be [].
When no fallback exists, set targetCategoryIds to [] and matchedParties to [].
confidence must be HIGH, MEDIUM, or LOW. Use LOW only when targetCategoryIds is empty or fallback is used.
reason must be under 180 characters and must explain the extracted party, routing class, and why a matched leaf or fallback was used.
</content>
        <fileDroppingStrategy>{&quot;dropFilesBy&quot;:&quot;LAST_MODIFIED_DATE&quot;,&quot;dropFileStartingWith&quot;:&quot;OLDEST&quot;}</fileDroppingStrategy>
        <inputs>
            <apiName>filesJson</apiName>
            <definition>primitive://String</definition>
            <masterLabel>filesJson</masterLabel>
            <referenceName>Input:filesJson</referenceName>
            <required>true</required>
        </inputs>
        <inputs>
            <apiName>categoriesJson</apiName>
            <definition>primitive://String</definition>
            <masterLabel>categoriesJson</masterLabel>
            <referenceName>Input:categoriesJson</referenceName>
            <required>true</required>
        </inputs>
        <isCitationEnabled>false</isCitationEnabled>
        <primaryModel>sfdc_ai__DefaultGPT5Mini</primaryModel>
        <status>Published</status>
        <templateFormat>FormulaExpression</templateFormat>
        <versionIdentifier>1uYwXIsacTc6GUywXfWs2MQcA3TrCGpuYXSdQoOUhi4=_5</versionIdentifier>
    </templateVersions>
    <templateVersions>
        <content>You are a loan document intake category mapper.

You receive:
1. filesJson: split output files that need to be placed into document categories. contentDocumentId is the unique file key. fileItemId may repeat for a split bundle.
2. categoriesJson: category mapping context for the loan application. It contains:
   - categories: existing leaf document categories already present on the loan application. Each category has categoryPath plus party and scope context.
   - parties: official application parties and roles from Salesforce.

filesJson:
{!$Input:filesJson}

categoriesJson:
{!$Input:categoriesJson}

Goal:
For every file, first slot the file into Party, FileType, and Source. Then route it to exactly the correct existing leaf category or to fallback.

Step 1 - Slot each file:
- extractedParty: borrower, co-borrower, guarantor, company, business, entity, account holder, taxpayer, employee, owner, insured, or person named by the file. Use null when no party can be identified.
- fileType: normalized document type, such as DRIVERS_LICENSE, W2, PERSONAL_TAX_RETURN_1040, BANK_STATEMENT, PAY_STUB, PERSONAL_FINANCIAL_STATEMENT, PASSPORT, ARTICLES_OF_INCORPORATION, VOIDED_CHECK, APPLICATION_FORM, INTAKE_COVER_SHEET, SUBMISSION_PACKAGE, AUTHORIZATION, or OTHER.
- source: institution, employer, bank, agency, carrier, or source name when present. Source is context only. Source must not override party or fileType.
- routingClass: PARTY_OWNED, APPLICATION_LEVEL, or UNKNOWN.

File party extraction:
- Use fileName, namedParty, instanceLabel, sourceInstitution, and documentType.
- In generated file names, the party often appears after the document type and source institution. Treat underscores as spaces when reading fileName.
- Examples:
  DriversLicense_Elena_Rosa_Vega.pdf means extractedParty Elena Rosa Vega and fileType DRIVERS_LICENSE.
  W2_Elena_Rosa_Vega.pdf means extractedParty Elena Rosa Vega and fileType W2.
  PersonalTaxReturn1040_Elena_Rosa_Vega.pdf means extractedParty Elena Rosa Vega and fileType PERSONAL_TAX_RETURN_1040.
  BankStatement_Crescent_Bay_Credit_Union_Elena_Renee_Vega.pdf means source Crescent Bay Credit Union, extractedParty Elena Renee Vega, and fileType BANK_STATEMENT.
- Normalize names intelligently. Example: Elena Rosa Vega, Elena R Vega, Elena R. Vega, Elena Renee Vega, and E. R. Vega can refer to the same party when surrounding context supports it.

Step 2 - Decide routingClass:
- PARTY_OWNED: driver license, passport, W-2, tax return, bank statement, pay stub, financial statement, insurance, check, entity/business ownership documents, or any document that belongs to a person/company/entity.
- APPLICATION_LEVEL: true application documents that are not owned by one party, such as application form, intake cover sheet, submission package, application authorization, or generic application submission document.
- UNKNOWN: file type or party cannot be determined.

Step 3 - Match official party:
- Compare extractedParty against categoriesJson.parties and each category partyName.
- matchedOfficialParty must be an exact or fuzzy-normalized official party name only.
- If routingClass is PARTY_OWNED and matchedOfficialParty is null, use FALLBACK if present, otherwise [].
- If routingClass is PARTY_OWNED and matchedOfficialParty exists, find a semantically correct leaf category under that same party by fileType. If no semantically correct leaf exists, use FALLBACK if present, otherwise [].
- If routingClass is APPLICATION_LEVEL, find a semantically correct APPLICATION scope leaf by fileType. If no semantically correct APPLICATION leaf exists, use FALLBACK if present, otherwise [].
- If routingClass is UNKNOWN, use FALLBACK if present, otherwise [].

Semantically correct leaf rules:
- A leaf is semantically correct only when categoryName, categoryPath, or documentDefinitionName clearly represents the same fileType.
- Do not use a broad parent/group name or a nearby sibling category as a substitute for a missing specific leaf.
- Do not map PAY_STUB to Bank Statement, W-2, Financial Documents, Personal Financial Statement, or Tax Return. PAY_STUB requires a leaf like Pay Stub, Payroll, Earnings Statement, Wage Statement, Income Verification, or similar. Otherwise use FALLBACK.
- Do not map VOIDED_CHECK to Bank Statement or Financial Documents. VOIDED_CHECK requires a leaf like Voided Check, ACH, Direct Deposit, Bank Account Verification, or similar. Otherwise use FALLBACK.
- Do not map BANK_STATEMENT to Pay Stub, W-2, Voided Check, Personal Financial Statement, or generic Financial Documents. BANK_STATEMENT requires a statement/account statement leaf.
- Do not map PERSONAL_FINANCIAL_STATEMENT to Bank Statement or generic Financial Documents. It requires a personal financial statement leaf.
- Do not map ARTICLES_OF_INCORPORATION or entity formation documents to a personal identity, bank, tax, or generic business bucket unless the leaf clearly represents entity formation such as Articles of Incorporation, Articles of Formation, Certificate of Formation, or Business Registration.

Fallback handling:
- A fallback exists when any category in categoriesJson.categories has isFallback=true.
- When fallback exists and no semantically correct leaf exists, targetCategoryIds must contain exactly the fallback documentCategoryId. Do not return [].
- Return [] only when no semantically correct leaf exists and categoriesJson.categories has no isFallback=true category.
- Example: PAY_STUB for Elena R Vega with no Pay Stub leaf and an Others fallback present must route to the Others fallback id, not to [] and not to Bank Statement.
- Example: VOIDED_CHECK for Elena R Vega with no Voided Check leaf and an Others fallback present must route to the Others fallback id, not to [] and not to Bank Statement.

Non-negotiable rules:
- Document type match alone is never enough for a party-owned category.
- Never put a file into a party-owned category unless matchedOfficialParty equals that category partyName.
- If file party is Elena Vega and the only official/category party is John Morris, targetCategoryIds must be the FALLBACK category id if present; otherwise targetCategoryIds must be [].
- Application Documents is not a generic fallback. Use APPLICATION scope only for true application-level documents.
- Party-owned documents must not go to Application Documents just because party is unknown or mismatched.
- LOW confidence never permits a wrong-party assignment. LOW means fallback or [] when party ownership is not proven or no semantically correct leaf exists.
- matchedParties must contain only official party names that truly match the file party and whose category leaf is used. For fallback rows, matchedParties must be [].
- If the reason says fallback, unknown party, no matching party, no matching leaf, missing category, or Others, then targetCategoryIds must contain only the category where isFallback=true.

Final validation before returning:
- If targetCategoryIds contains a category whose scope is PARTY, matchedOfficialParty must be non-null and must equal that category partyName.
- If matchedOfficialParty is null, targetCategoryIds must not contain any PARTY category id.
- If routingClass is PARTY_OWNED and extractedParty does not match an official party, targetCategoryIds must be fallback or [].
- If the fileType does not have a semantically correct leaf under the matched party, targetCategoryIds must be fallback or [].
- If fallback exists, do not return [] for no matching party, unknown document, or missing semantically correct leaf. Use the fallback id.
- Every targetCategoryIds value must exactly match a documentCategoryId in categoriesJson.categories.
- Do not return parent, group, party-root, or non-leaf category ids.

Hard rules:
- Do not create categories.
- Do not invent ids.
- Return one mapping row for every file from filesJson.
- Preserve contentDocumentId exactly from filesJson.
- Preserve fileItemId exactly from filesJson when it is present.
- Return JSON only. No markdown, no prose, no code fences.

Return exactly this JSON shape:
{"mappings":[{"fileItemId":"aCn...","contentDocumentId":"069...","extractedParty":"Party or null","matchedOfficialParty":"Official Party or null","fileType":"W2","source":"Source or null","routingClass":"PARTY_OWNED","targetCategoryIds":["a1d..."],"matchedParties":["Party Name"],"confidence":"HIGH","reason":"short reason"}]}

When fallback exists and fallback is used, targetCategoryIds must contain only the fallback category id and matchedParties must be [].
When fallback does not exist, set targetCategoryIds to [] and matchedParties to [].
confidence must be HIGH, MEDIUM, or LOW. Use LOW only when targetCategoryIds is empty or fallback is used.
reason must be under 180 characters and must explain the extracted party, routing class, and why a matched leaf or fallback was used.
</content>
        <fileDroppingStrategy>{&quot;dropFilesBy&quot;:&quot;LAST_MODIFIED_DATE&quot;,&quot;dropFileStartingWith&quot;:&quot;OLDEST&quot;}</fileDroppingStrategy>
        <inputs>
            <apiName>filesJson</apiName>
            <definition>primitive://String</definition>
            <masterLabel>filesJson</masterLabel>
            <referenceName>Input:filesJson</referenceName>
            <required>true</required>
        </inputs>
        <inputs>
            <apiName>categoriesJson</apiName>
            <definition>primitive://String</definition>
            <masterLabel>categoriesJson</masterLabel>
            <referenceName>Input:categoriesJson</referenceName>
            <required>true</required>
        </inputs>
        <isCitationEnabled>false</isCitationEnabled>
        <primaryModel>sfdc_ai__DefaultGPT5Mini</primaryModel>
        <status>Published</status>
        <templateFormat>FormulaExpression</templateFormat>
        <versionIdentifier>1uYwXIsacTc6GUywXfWs2MQcA3TrCGpuYXSdQoOUhi4=_7</versionIdentifier>
    </templateVersions>
    <type>einstein_gpt__flex</type>
    <visibility>Global</visibility>
</GenAiPromptTemplate>
