<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<GenAiPromptTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <description>Drafts a short, polite email to the borrower listing missing documents and quality issues that need attention.</description>
    <developerName>AIDocBorrowerEmail</developerName>
    <masterLabel>AI Doc Borrower Email</masterLabel>
    <overridable>false</overridable>
    <templateVersions>
        <content>You are a loan officer&apos;s assistant drafting a short, polite, professional email to a borrower asking them to provide missing or replacement documents.

Recipient: {!$Input:borrowerName}

The recipient&apos;s coverage data (categories required vs. on file vs. missing) is:
{!$Input:coverageJson}

Per-file classification verdicts (already known to be the correct document type when OK):
{!$Input:verdictsText}

Per-file sanity findings (quality, completeness, borrower-identity, recency, expiry):
{!$Input:sanityFindingsText}

Write a single email body (no subject line, no salutation block separately, no closing block separately — just one continuous email body). Follow these rules:

1. Start with &quot;Dear {!$Input:borrowerName},&quot;.
2. One short opening sentence saying we&apos;re reviewing their application and need their help to complete it.
3. A &quot;Documents we still need:&quot; section as a bulleted list of EVERY category that is missing (from coverageJson&apos;s missingCategoryNames).
4. A &quot;Documents that need replacement or update:&quot; section as a bulleted list of files that have a sanity issue. Include items from sanityFindingsText where the verdict is one of: WRONG_BORROWER, INCOMPLETE, STALE, EXPIRED, EXPIRING_SOON, UNREADABLE. For each, briefly explain what&apos;s wrong in plain language (no technical labels — say &quot;we received only one month&quot; not &quot;INCOMPLETE&quot;). Skip this whole section if there are no issues.
5. Do NOT mention documents that are OK. Do NOT mention documents that passed both classification and sanity.
6. One short closing sentence thanking them and offering to help.
7. Sign off with &quot;Best regards,\nYour Loan Officer&quot;.

Rules:
- Keep the entire email under 200 words.
- Be warm but professional. No exclamation marks.
- Do not invent categories or details not present in the inputs.
- If both missing list AND issues list would be empty, write a short note saying we have everything we need and will be in touch shortly.

Output the email body as plain text only (no markdown, no HTML, no quotes around the body).

</content>
        <fileDroppingStrategy>{&quot;dropFilesBy&quot;:&quot;LAST_MODIFIED_DATE&quot;,&quot;dropFileStartingWith&quot;:&quot;OLDEST&quot;}</fileDroppingStrategy>
        <inputs>
            <apiName>borrowerName</apiName>
            <definition>primitive://String</definition>
            <masterLabel>borrowerName</masterLabel>
            <referenceName>Input:borrowerName</referenceName>
            <required>true</required>
        </inputs>
        <inputs>
            <apiName>coverageJson</apiName>
            <definition>primitive://String</definition>
            <masterLabel>coverageJson</masterLabel>
            <referenceName>Input:coverageJson</referenceName>
            <required>true</required>
        </inputs>
        <inputs>
            <apiName>verdictsText</apiName>
            <definition>primitive://String</definition>
            <masterLabel>verdictsText</masterLabel>
            <referenceName>Input:verdictsText</referenceName>
            <required>true</required>
        </inputs>
        <inputs>
            <apiName>sanityFindingsText</apiName>
            <definition>primitive://String</definition>
            <masterLabel>sanityFindingsText</masterLabel>
            <referenceName>Input:sanityFindingsText</referenceName>
            <required>true</required>
        </inputs>
        <isCitationEnabled>false</isCitationEnabled>
        <primaryModel>sfdc_ai__DefaultGPT5Mini</primaryModel>
        <status>Published</status>
        <versionIdentifier>1uYwXIsacTc6GUywXfWs2MQcA3TrCGpuYXSdQoOUhi4=_1</versionIdentifier>
    </templateVersions>
    <type>einstein_gpt__flex</type>
    <visibility>Global</visibility>
</GenAiPromptTemplate>
